intercallonline.com 2011-05-26

# InterCall Privacy Policy | Conference Call Company

InterCall is a leading provider of audio and Web conferencing services. We have developed this website (the “InterCall Site”) to provide you with access to these services. We understand your need for privacy when using the Web for your communication. This policy discloses InterCall’s practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of user information collected through the InterCall Site and through your use of InterCall services.

**1\. USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.** In connection with the operation of the InterCall site we may ask you to provide us with information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you ("Personal Information") when, among other things, you register on the InterCall site, use one of our services, fill out a survey, make a request for information, or enter a sweepstakes or contest through the InterCall Site. We will use the Personal Information you provide us in these circumstances to operate the InterCall site, to satisfy InterCall's legitimate business interests, such as customer analysis and internal marketing study and analysis, and to provide information you request from the InterCall Site ("Primary Use"). Unless you instruct us not to do so, InterCall may also use the Personal Information you provide us to contact you regarding additional or new services and features offered by InterCall, special offers by InterCall, or important information regarding InterCall ("InterCall Secondary Use"). In addition, with your permission, we may provide your Personal Information to other companies who may contact you regarding products, services, and offers that may be of interest to you, but that are not directly related to InterCall or the InterCall Site (“Third Party Secondary Use”).

InterCall may provide Personal Information to vendors that assist InterCall in processing the information. InterCall requires such vendors to enter into agreements with InterCall prohibiting disclosure of the information to others and restricting its use to providing the contracted services of InterCall.

**2\. CHOICE.** As we noted above, we will not use your Personal Information for any Third Party Secondary Uses unless you affirmatively choose to participate in such Secondary Uses. You may also stop delivery of informational or promotional mail from us by following the instructions included in the informational or promotional mail itself.

**3\. ACCESS.** When you register to use any of the services offered by InterCall, InterCall will send you a confirmation of your registration showing the Personal Information we obtained from your registration. Also, we will take reasonable steps to give you the opportunity to correct inaccuracies in the Personal Information we retain concerning you and delete Personal Information concerning you upon your request.

**4\. SECURITY.** The Personal Information we collect from you is stored in operating environments that employ reasonable security measures and that are not available to the general public. InterCall is not responsible for unauthorized access to such information by hackers or others that obtain access through illegal measures, in the absence of negligence on the part of InterCall. Further, the other sites you may access through the InterCall Site may have different security practices and you should familiarize yourself with those practices.

You are responsible for the confidentiality and security of passwords InterCall issues to you. If you believe a third party has obtained your password in an unauthorized manner, please notify us promptly.

**5\. COMPLAINTS.** If at any time you believe we have acted contrary to this Privacy Policy, please notify us by e-mail at [website@intercall.com](mailto:website@intercall.com) and we will take steps to investigate and will use reasonable measures to remedy the problem.

**6\. DISCLOSURE FOR LEGAL PURPOSES.** We may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief such action is necessary: (a) to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates; (b) to protect and defend our rights or property or those of our users; (c) to protect the personal safety of our users or the public; or (d) in connection with a merger, consolidation or sale of substantial assets of InterCall. As we continue to develop our business, we might buy or sell assets related to our business. In such transactions Personal Information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event InterCall or substantially all of its assets are acquired, Personal Information will be one of the transferred assets.

**7\. ANONYMOUS INFORMATION.** Please understand, in addition to collecting Personal Information, InterCall will also gather information that does not personally identify you regarding your use of the InterCall Site ("Anonymous Information"). The Anonymous Information we collect regarding your use of the InterCall Site may be used by us to measure the effectiveness of marketing efforts on the InterCall Site, for improving the services we offer to you, or to improve the InterCall Site. Generally, you will not be aware when such Anonymous Information is being collected about you - it may be collected in various ways, such as through traffic data or direct surveys of our customers and may entail the use of, among other things, cookies, IP addresses, or other numeric codes used to identify the computer or other device used to access our site.

**8\. COOKIES.** We use cookies to provide you with better service. Cookies are pieces of information a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for recordkeeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences for a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major websites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of the functionality of the InterCall Site or services if you do so.

**9\. VENTURING OFF THE INTERCALL SITE.** The InterCall Site may contain hyperlinks that can take you to websites run by third parties ("Third-Party Sites"). Any hypertext or other links to Third-Party Sites from the InterCall Site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the InterCall Site. InterCall has not reviewed all of these Third-Party Sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites or their content or practices. Thus, InterCall does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software, or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the Third-Party Sites linked to the InterCall Site, you do this entirely at your own risk.

Remember, this Privacy Policy only applies to the InterCall Site. When you are no longer on the InterCall Site, you may encounter different privacy and security practices and you should familiarize yourself with those practices each time you visit a new site.

**10\. MODIFICATIONS.** InterCall reserves the right to modify the Privacy Policy at any time. Please review the Privacy Policy each time you use the InterCall Site, as your continued use of the InterCall Site and the services signifies your assent to such modifications.

**11\. CONTACT US.** If at any time you believe InterCall has not followed the above policy, please contact us via e-mail at [website@intercall.com](mailto:website@intercall.com).

* * *

## HIPAA PRIVACY NOTICE

THIS NOTICE DESCRIBES HOW MEDICAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU MAY BE USED AND DISCLOSED AND HOW YOU CAN OBTAIN ACCESS TO THIS INFORMATION. PLEASE REVIEW IT CAREFULLY.

**INTRODUCTION**

West Corporation and its affiliates are required by law to maintain the privacy of "protected health information." "Protected health information" includes any identifiable information we obtain from you or others that relates to your physical or mental health, the health care you have received, or payment for your health care.

As required by law, this notice provides you with information about your rights and our legal duties and privacy practices with respect to the privacy of protected health information. This notice also discusses the uses and disclosures we will make of your protected health information. We must comply with the provisions of this notice, although we reserve the right to change the terms of this notice from time to time and to make the revised notice effective for all protected health information we maintain. You can always request a copy of the most current privacy notice from our Privacy and Security Official.

This Notice applies to the following organizations that are affiliated as part of West Corporation and share similar information practices:

  * West Corporation 
  * A Better Conference, Inc. 
  * Asset Direct Mortgage, LLC 
  * BuyDebtCo, LLC 
  * Cosmosis Corporation 
  * InterCall, Inc. 
  * InterCall Telecom Ventures, LLC 
  * Intrado, Inc. 
  * Intrado Command Systems, Inc. 
  * Intrado Communications, Inc. 
  * Intrado Communications of Virginia, Inc. 
  * Intrado Information Systems Holdings, Inc. 
  * Intrado International, LLC 
  * Northern Contact, Inc. 
  * Positron Public Safety Systems Corp. 
  * Stargate Management, LLC 
  * Stream57 Corporation 
  * TeleVox Software, Incorporated 
  * The Debt Depot, LLC 
  * West Asset Management, Inc. 
  * West Asset Purchasing, LLC 
  * West At Home, LLC 
  * West Business Services, LLC 
  * West Customer Management Group, LLC 
  * West Direct, LLC 
  * West Direct II, Inc. 
  * West Education Foundation 
  * West Facilities, LLC 
  * West Interactive Corporation 
  * West International Corporation 
  * West Notifications Group, Inc. 
  * West Receivables, LLC 
  * West Receivables Holdings, LLC 
  * West Receivables Purchasing, LLC 
  * West Receivables Services, Inc. 
  * Worldwide Asset Purchasing, LLC

* * *

**PERMITTED USES AND DISCLOSURES**

The affiliates of West Corporation (“West”) listed above are Business Associates of Covered Entities with which you may do business. These Covered Entities would include, for example, your insurance company, your dentist, your pharmacy, etc. In the capacity of Business Associate, the Covered Entity you use may provide access to a portion of your protected health information to West. We intend to use or disclose your protected health information for the purposes of fulfilling our obligations to the Covered Entity. These uses or disclosures may include, but are not limited to, the following categories and examples:

 **Treatment** – We may use protected health information provided to us by your Covered Entity to inform you of approaching events related to your healthcare. For example, we may notify you a prescription is coming up for refill; or, we may call you because it has been a while since you have ordered supplies for a medical condition and it is time to reorder.

 **Payment** – We may use protected health information provided to us by your Covered Entity to inform you of issues related to payment for your healthcare. For example, we may notify you of a past due payment on a medical bill.

 **Healthcare operations** – We may use protected health information provided to us by your Covered Entity to assist your Covered Entity in serving you better. For example, we may provide conference capabilities for your physician to consult with other medical staff; we may provide customer service on behalf of your insurance carrier to assist you with your insurance benefits; or, we may provide recall notifications for a recalled medical device you may use.

* * *

**OTHER USES AND DISCLOSURES OF PROTECTED HEALTH INFORMATION**

We may contact you, on behalf of your Covered Entity, to provide appointment reminders or information about health-related benefits and services that may be of interest to you.

We may disclose your protected health information at the direction of your Covered Entity and only as permitted by applicable law. This may include disclosure of your protected health information to your family or friends or any other individual identified by you when they are involved in your care or the payment of your care. We will only disclose the protected health information directly relevant to their involvement in your care or payment. We may also use or disclose your protected health information to notify, or assist in the notification of, a family member, a personal representative, or another person responsible for your care of your location, general condition or death. If you are available, we will give you an opportunity to object to these disclosures, and we will not make these disclosures if you object. If you are not available, we will determine whether a disclosure to your family or friends is in your best interest, and we will disclose only the protected health information that is directly relevant to their involvement in your care.

When permitted by law, we may coordinate our uses and disclosures of protected health information with public or private entities authorized by law or by charter to assist in disaster relief efforts.

We may contact you on behalf of your Covered Entity as part of their marketing efforts as permitted by applicable law.

* * *

**SPECIAL SITUATIONS**

Except for the special situations set forth below and the general uses and disclosures described above, we will not use or disclose your protected health information for any other purposes unless you provide a written authorization to your Covered Entity.

 **Worker’s Compensation** – We may disclose your protected health information to the extent authorized by and to the extent necessary to comply with laws relating to workers’ compensation or other similar programs established by law.

 **Public Health** – When required or permitted by law, we may disclose your protected health information to public health or legal authorities responsible for preventing or controlling disease, injury or disability or performing other public health functions. In addition, we may disclose your protected health information in order to avert a serious threat to health or safety.

 **Specialized Government Functions** – We may disclose your protected health information for military and veterans’ activities, national security and intelligence activities and similar special governmental functions as required or permitted by law.

 **Health Oversight Agencies** – We may disclose your protected health information to an appropriate health oversight agency, public health authority or attorney involved in health oversight activities.

 **Law Enforcement** – We may disclose your protected health information for law enforcement purposes as required or permitted by law or in response to a valid subpoena, court order or other binding authority.

 **Judicial and Administrative Proceedings** – We may disclose your protected health information for judicial or administrative proceedings as required or permitted by law or in response to a valid subpoena, court order or other binding authority.

 **Food and Drug Administration (“FDA”)** – We may disclose to the FDA, or an entity subject to FDA jurisdiction, your protected health information for public health purposes related to the quality, safety or effectiveness of an FDA-regulated product or activity for which that person has responsibility. For example, your information may be disclosed in connection with the reporting of an adverse event, product defect, product tracking or to provide post marketing surveillance information.

 **Disclosures Required by Law** – We may use or disclose your protected health information as required by law provided such use or disclosure complies with and is limited to the relevant requirements of such law.

* * *

**YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING HEALTH INFORMATION ABOUT YOU**

You have a right to expect your protected health information will be kept secure and used only for legitimate purposes. 

  * You have a right to understand how your protected health information may be used and disclosed by West. 
  * You have a right to access this privacy notice that tells you how your protected health information may be used or disclosed. 
  * You have a right to ask questions about any health privacy issue and have those questions clearly and promptly answered. 
  * You have a (limited) right to know who has seen your health information, and for what purpose. If you make additional requests for such an accounting during any 12-month period, we may charge you a reasonable, cost-based fee. 
  * You have a right to see, and to keep a copy of, all of your health records except psychotherapy notes and information compiled in reasonable anticipation of, or for use in, a civil, criminal, or administrative action or proceeding. Your request for a copy of your record must be in writing. 
  * You have a right to ask for correction or inclusion of a statement of disagreement for anything in your records you feel is in error. Your request must be submitted in writing and include supporting documentation. 
  * You have a right to authorize, or refuse, additional uses of your protected health information, such as for fundraising, marketing, or research. 
  * You have a right to request extra protections for protected health information you consider especially sensitive, and to request we communicate with you by alternative means.

* * *

**COMPLAINTS**

If you believe your privacy rights have been violated, you should immediately contact our Privacy and Security Official. We will not take any action against you for filing a complaint. You may also file a complaint with the Secretary of Health and Human Services.

 **CONTACT PERSON**

If you have any questions or would like further information about this notice, please contact Alain Zarinelli, West Corporation Privacy and Security Official, at (402) 963-1200 or by mail at 11808 Miracle Hills Drive, Omaha, NE 68154.
